Audiovisual Collection RRFA.02 RRFA.02.TEST2
RRF Test Repository
- Performance, 1954 - 2009; 8.45 Cubic Feet; 149 Video Recordings 90 analog video recordings; 59 digital surrogates; 29 Motion Picture Films; 12 Sound Recordings
  - Rauschenberg, Robert
    - "Shot Put"
      - Sound track, 1964; 0.03 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings acetate audio tape 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 8, Reg number 64.A001.00)
    - "Spring Training"
      - Sound track, 1965; 0.038 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings acetate audio tape; 3.75 ips 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 31, Reg number 65.A002.00)
    - Compilations
      - "Canoe," "Linoleum," "Map Room [II?]," "Pelican," "[Open Score?]", circa 1963-1966; 0.12 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films B&W; positive, silent 16 mm; 1 Video Recordings digital betacam transfer (Box 45, Object 2, Reg number 66.MM002.01, Box 8, Object 10)
      - "Pelican" and "Spring Training" sound tracks and RR intros, 1963, 1965; 0.016 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings acetate audio tape; 3.75 ips 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 7, Reg number 65.A001.00)
      - "Robert Rauschenberg: Performance 1954-1995", 1997; Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum; Brown, Trisha, 1936-; Cunningham, Merce; Taylor, Paul, 1930-; 0.161 Cubic Feet; 11 Video Recordings 3 analog duplication master, exhibition master and copy, 4 analog access copies and 4 digital surrogates; 00:46:58; 00:07:19; 00:46:58; 00:15:03 (Box 8, Object 21, Object 22, Reg number 97.V016.01, Box 30, Object 30, Object 23, Reg number 97.V016.02, Object 24, Box 57, Object 2)
        Recording includes excerpts of "Pelican," "Map Room II," "Linoleum," and "Spring Training."
      - "Robert Rauschenberg: The Art of Performance", 1997; Guilfoyle, Ultan; Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum; 0.24 Cubic Feet; 12 Video Recordings 2 analog masters, 6 analog duplicates and 4 digital surrogates; 01:07:26; 01:07:26; 00:35:18; 00:48:31 (Box 8, Object 23, Reg number 97.V030.00, Object 24, Reg number 97.V030.02, Object 4, Reg number 97.V014.02, Object 5, Object 6, Reg number 99.V001.00, Object 25, Reg number 97.V014.03, Object 26, Object 27, Reg number 97.V014.01)
  - Various
    - 9 Evenings, "Pelican," Map Room," "Linoleum", undated (Box 43, Object 8, Reg number 66.MM002.00, Box 8, Object 9)
    - "Beyond the Mainstream." Dance in America. WNET., 1980; Brown, Trisha, 1936-; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934-; Paxton, Steve; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate of broadcast video recording (Box 8, Object 8)
    - First New York Theater Rally and Expanded Film Festival, 1965 May and December; Hay, Alex; Hay, Deborah; Paxton, Steve; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate of B&W 16 mm film; 00:14:03
      The recording contains footage from Alex Hay's "Leadville," Deborah Hay's Will They or Won't They" and "Victory 14," Steve Paxton's "Flat," and Robert Rauschenberg's "Map Room II" and "Pelican."
    - "Leadville," "Pelican" and unidentified, circa 1963-1966; 0.104 Cubic Feet; 2 Motion Picture Films B&W; positive; optical sound track 16 mm; 2 Video Recordings 2 digital betacam transfers (Box 44, Object 6, Reg number 63.MM001.00, Object 7, Reg number 63.MM002.00, Box 8, Object 12, Object 13)
      Hay, Alex
    - "Linoleum," plus slides of "Minutiae" and "Travelogue" sets, 1954, 1966, 1977; 1984 December 18; Cunningham, Merce; 0.05 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog video compilation and digital surrogate; 00:15:16 (Box 37, Object 14, Reg number 66.V010.00)
    - "The Judson Project." Bennington College., circa 1983; Brown, Trisha, 1936-; Paxton, Steve; 2 Video Recordings digital surrogates; 01:00:06; 00:32:23
      Brown, Trisha, 1936-; Paxton, Steve
- Personal/Biographical, 1967 - 2008; 9.39 Cubic Feet; 247 Video Recordings 129 analog video recordings; 118 digital surrogates; 36 Motion Picture Films; 34 Sound Recordings
  Recordings in Series 7. Personal and Biographical relate to Rauschenberg's personal life and narrative. These materials include personal recordings made by the artist of his travels and celebrations with friends, biographical works and news coverage describing Rauschenberg's career and influence, and award ceremonies given in his honor. Other recordings include artist statements and biographies made by the artist, interviews and lectures he gave, and testimonies delivered before the U.S. Congress. Highlights include Super 8 films of Rauschenberg's home in Captiva and source materials from the unfinished Jacques Clement film "Mostly About Rauschenberg" that feature Rauschenberg talking about his work. The series is comprised of one hundred twenty-nine analog video recordings, thirty-four 16 mm films, thirty-four sound recordings, two Super 8 films, and one hundred eighteen digital videos and surrogates.
  This series has been arranged alphabetically into the following sub-series: Awards, Biography, Films, Home movies and sound recordings, Instructional videos, Interviews, Lectures and Symposia, Legal, Memorial, Radio, Social and political, and Television and serials. Cross-references are provided for agents and subjects which appear elsewhere in the archives.
  - Awards
    - Algur H. Meadows Award, Southern Methodist University, 1989; 0.07 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings 3 analog compilations and 2 digital surrogates; 0:30:00; 00:14:10; 00:35:56 (Box 8, Object 9, Reg number 90.V004.01, Object 10, Reg number 89.V025.00, Box 37, Object 15, Reg number 90.V004.00)
    - Arts for ACT, 2002 August 24; Tomlin, Lily; 0.06 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings distribution copies (Box 8, Object 11, Object 12, Object 28)
      Tomlin, Lily
    - International Sculpture Center Award, New York Times FLA, 1996; 0.005 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings raw footage; camera original (Box 32, Object 6, Reg number 96.V004.00)
    - Medal Award, School of the Museum of Fine Arts, 2002 May; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings (Box 8, Object 13)
      Close, Chuck, 1940-
    - Medal of Merit, The Lotos Club, 1991; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings (Box 33, Object 7, Reg number 91.A001.00)
    - National Arts Club, 1989 January 11; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate (Box 8, Object 19, Reg number 89.V027.00)
    - Wexner Prize, Wexner Center for the Arts, 2000; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings (Box 8, Object 20, Object 21, Reg number 200.V009.00)
      See also: Wexner Prize lectures
  - Biography
    - "Robert Rauschenberg", 1985; 0.58 Cubic Feet; 13 Video Recordings 12 analog video recordings and 1 digital surrogate; 0:22:00; 00:22:31 (Box 37, Object 16, Reg number 84.V002.00, Object 17, Reg number 91.V012.02, Object 18, Reg number 91.V012.01, Object 22, Reg number 91.V012.00, Object 1, Reg number 91.V012.03, Object 2, Object 3, Object 4, Object 5, Object 6, Box 8, Object 7, Object 19)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg" Spanish Version, 1985; 0.12 Cubic Feet; 6 Video Recordings duplicates; 03:00:00 (Box 8, Object 7, Object 8, Reg number 85.V093.00, Object 9, Reg number 90.V010.00, Object 10, Object 11, Object 12, Reg number 88.V007.00)
    - Statements about Art, Life, etc., 1975 March; Taylor, Debbie (Skorupa); 0.05 Cubic Feet; 3 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 7.5 ips; stereo; synch (2 tapes) 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 9, Reg number 75.A003.02, Object 32, Reg number 75.A003.00, Object 33, Reg number 75.A003.01)
      May be related to "Mostly About Rauschenberg."
      Taylor, Debbie (Skorupa)
  - Films
    - "Amerikanarna på och Pontus Hulthén -Konsten Moderna Museet", 1998; 2010; Schultz-Lundestam, Barbro; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings distribution copy; NTSC; 00:48:00 (Box 8, Object 13, Reg number 98.V011.00)
      HulteÌn, Pontus, 1924-2006; Klüver, Billy, 1927-2004
    - "East Village", 1968; Fahlström, Öyvind, 1928-1976; 2 Video Recordings digital surrogates; B&W; 00:39:03; 00:03:40
      Hay, Alex; Hay, Deborah
    - "Ich Muss Unsichtbar Werden", 1998 December 5; Wehrli, Peter K., 1939-; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings interfiled correspondence duplicates; mono; NTSC (Box 8, Object 14, Object 15)
    - "Mostly About Rauschenberg", Clemente, Jacques; Thompson, Mayo; Kozlov, Christine
      - Elements
        - "Captiva filming: Room sounds: Radio/TV, People background, paper motor", 1974 September 14; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 7.5 ips; mono 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 34)
        - "Debbie", circa 1975; 0.14 Cubic Feet; 2 Sound Recordings full magnetic coat and B&W optical sound track; no images 16 mm (Box 46, Object 2, Reg number 75.MM001.14, Box 48, Object 9, Reg number 75.MM001.00)
        - "Eye on Art", circa 1967; 0.35 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog film transfer masters; composites and outtakes 1 inch; 0.21 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive; silent 16 mm (Box 50, Object 7, Reg number 75.MM001.09, Box 10, Object 1, Reg number 85.M001.04, Object 2, Reg number 85.M001.03)
        - "Four Pairs", circa 1975; 0.12 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive 16 mm; 1 Sound Recordings B&W; optical sound track; no images at head 16 mm (Box 46, Object 2, Reg number 75.MM001.14, Box 48, Object 11, Reg number 75.MM001.02)
        - [Hoarfrosts], circa 1974; 0.14 Cubic Feet; 2 Motion Picture Films color; positive; 1 silent and 1 optical sound track; no sound at head 16 mm (Box 46, Object 4, Reg number 75.MM001.13, Object 5, Reg number 75.MM001.06)
        - "N.Y. House Roof Sounds (Jet plane); Beach Sounds", circa 1970s; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 7.5 and 3.75 ips; mono and stereo; 60 cycle sync (Box 35, Object 35)
        - [Statement at 381 kitchen table], circa 1978; 0.01 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive; silent 16 mm; 1 Sound Recordings full magnetic coat 16 mm (Box 48, Object 13, Reg number 78.MM002.01)
        - [Statement on Captiva beach], circa 1975; 0.52 Cubic Feet; 6 Motion Picture Films color; positive; 3 optical sound tracks and 3 silent 16 mm; 1 Sound Recordings full magnetic coat 16 mm (Box 46, Object 6, Reg number 75.MM001.15, Object 7, Box 47, Object 4, Reg number 75.MM001.08, Box 48, Object 13, Reg number 78.MM002.01, Box 50, Object 5, Reg number 75.MM001.04, Reg number 75.MM001.07)
        - Titles, circa 1975; 0.02 Motion Picture Films; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive; silent 16 mm (Box 46, Object 2, Reg number 75.MM001.14)
        - Unidentified
          - Artworks, circa 1975, 1978; 0.42 Cubic Feet; 6 Motion Picture Films color; positive; 5 silent and 1 optical sound track 16 mm (Box 46, Object 1, Reg number 75.MM001.11, Box 47, Reg number 78.MM002.02, Object 3, Reg number 75.MM001.05, Box 48, Object 10, Reg number 75.MM001.16, Object 15, Reg number 75.MM001.01)
            May be related to "Robert Rauschenberg." Monitor, Episode 127.
          - Audio, circa 1975; 1.27 Cubic Feet; 17 Sound Recordings 16 full magnetic coat films and 1 polyester audio tape 16 mm; 1/4 inch (Box 45, Object 1, Reg number 75.A002.08, Object 5, Object 6, Object 7, Reg number 75.A002.03, Object 8, Reg number 75.A002.04, Box 46, Object 2, Reg number 75.MM001.14, Box 48, Object 13, Reg number 78.MM002.01, Object 14, Reg number 75.A002.11, Box 49, Reg number 75.A002.00, Reg number 75.A002.01, Object 3, Reg number 75.A002.05, Object 4, Reg number 75.A002.06, Reg number 75.A002.09, Object 10, Reg number 75.A002.10, Box 52, Reg number 75.A002.12, Reg number 75.A002.02)
          - "Rausch.", circa 1975; 0.104 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; negative 16 mm; 1 Video Recordings (Box 48, Object 12, Reg number 75.MM001.12, Box 8, Object 8)
      - Derivatives
        - Composite, circa 1975; 0.002 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings digital surrogates from window burn video recording; 00:28:53 (Box 30, Object 18)
          Panning views of studio and artworks.
        - Excerpts, circa 1975; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings excerpts; analog video recording and digital surrogate; B&W; 00:07:01 (Box 12, Object 16)
          Footage of Bob talking, making "Hoarfrosts."
        - Film transfers, 1985 January 25; 0.05 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings 1 analog window burn film transfer and 2 digital surrogates; 00:26:54; 00:32:16 (Box 37, Object 6, Reg number 85.V042)
        - Full film?, circa 1975; 0.21 Cubic Feet; 2 Motion Picture Films color; original negative and positive; optical sound 16 mm; 1 Video Recordings (Box 55, Object 2, Reg number 75.MM001.10; 85.MM001.15, Box 46, Object 3, Reg number 75.MM001.03, Box 8)
      - Panel
        - Haus de Kunst panel, 2008 October 6; Thompson, Mayo; White, David; 1 Sound Recordings 00:41:19 (Box 30, Object 19, Reg number 208.V005)
          Thompson, Mayo; White, David
    - "Painter's Painting: A Candid History of the New York Art Scene, 1940-1970" excerpt, 1973; De Antonio, Emile; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate; B&W and color; 00:09:56
    - "Pop Art etc.", circa 2001; Cornand, Brigitte; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings interfiled business card duplicate (Box 8, Object 17, Reg number 201.V002.00)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg at Gemini", 1984 July 20; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings raw footage (Box 8, Object 18)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg: Man at Work", 1997; 0.06 Cubic Feet; 7 Video Recordings 3 analog distribution and access copies; 4 digital surrogates; NTSC; 00:04:00; 01:01:35; 00:03:12; 00:04:27 (Box 8, Object 20, Reg number 97.015.02, Object 21, Reg number 97.V015.01; 97.V015.02, Object 22, Reg number 97.V015.03)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg: Technology is Just Another Brush", 1988; Krüger, Werner; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog video recording and digital surrogate; 01:26:10 (Box 8, Object 7, Reg number 85.V092.00)
    - "Who gets to call it art?: the legend of Henry Geldzahler, 1935-1994." Peter Rosen. Muse Film and Television., 2005; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate; 01:18:34
  - Home movies and sound recordings
    - Beachhouse Music: Kat, Bob and Bob, 1989; 0.005 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings raw footage; camera original (Box 30, Object 7, Reg number 89.V027.00)
    - Birthdays, 1989-1992; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 4 Video Recordings 3 camera originals and 1 compilation (Box 8, Object 23, Reg number 91.V036.00, Box 30, Object 8, Reg number 90.V002.00, Object 9, Reg number 91.V034.00, Object 10, Reg number 91.V033.00)
    - Captiva studio: R #3, undated; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 15 ips? 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 36)
      Related materials
    - Captiva Waves, undated; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive; silent Super 8 (Box 41, Object 10)
    - Debbie Taylor telling stories in 381 kitchen, circa 1975; Taylor, Debbie (Skorupa); 0.11 Cubic Feet; 3 Motion Picture Films 1 B&W film with optical sound track, 1 color negative silent film and 1 color positive silent film 16 mm (Box 48, Object 6, Reg number 75.MM002.01, Object 7, Reg number 75.MM002.02, Object 8, Reg number 75.MM002.03)
    - Greece, 1989 May 14-17, undated; 0.06 Cubic Feet; 8 Video Recordings raw footage; camera originals (Box 30, Object 11, Reg number 89.V015.00, Object 12, Reg number 89.V016.00, Object 13, Reg number 89.V017.00, Object 14, Reg number 89.V018.00, Object 15, Reg number 89.V019.00, Object 16, Reg number 89.V020.00, Object 17, Reg number 89.V021.00, Object 18, Reg number 89.V022.00)
    - Happy Birthday Bob (From Merce), 2005; Cunningham, Merce; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings home recording (Box 8, Object 21, Reg number 205.V003.00)
      Video birthday message featuring Merce Cunningham.
    - Jungle Road, Captiva, undated; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Motion Picture Films color; positive; silent Super 8 (Box 41, Object 9)
    - Leo and [Toiny] Castelli House: Bed, Pantomime, Crocus, 1974 September 21; Castelli, Leo; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; stereo 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 10, Reg number 74.A001.00)
      Castelli, Leo
    - New Gulf House, circa 1990; 0.005 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings raw footage; camera original (Box 30, Object 19)
    - NY Sound Track, undated; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 3.75 ips; mono 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 37)
    - Party: Party Music, circa 1960s; 0.008 Cubic Feet; 1 Sound Recordings acetate audio tape 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 11)
      May be related to "Party" performance at Judson Dance Theater.
    - Windsurfing, circa 1980s; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings home recording (Box 8, Object 20)
    - X-Mass, 1989-1992; 0.03 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings 2 camera originals and 1 compilaton (Box 8, Object 23, Reg number 91.V036.00, Box 30, Object 20, Reg number 91.V017.00, Object 21, Reg number 91.V018.00)
  - Instructional videos
    - "Fauve Xpress," "Health Rider," "Murad", undated; 0.06 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings distribution copies (Box 8, Object 23, Object 24, Object 25)
  - Interviews
    - "Close/Rauschenberg." Charlie Rose, Episode 8040. PBS., 1998; Rose, Charlie; 0.08 Cubic Feet; 4 Video Recordings raw footage duplicates (Box 8, Object 5, Reg number 98.V018.00, Object 6, Reg number 98.V018.01, Object 7, Reg number 98.V018.02, Object 8, Reg number 98.V018.03)
      Rose, Charlie; Close, Chuck, 1940-
    - "Conversations with Artists: Robert Rauschenberg." National Gallery of Art., 1985 January 6; Fine, Ruth, 1941-; Saff, Donald, 1937-; Rosenthal, Nan; 0.14 Cubic Feet; 5 Video Recordings 2 analog masters, 2 analog access copies and 1 excerpted digital surrogate (Box 37, Object 2, Reg number 85.V115.00, Object 3, Reg number 85.V002.00, Box 8, Object 29, Object 30)
      Fine, Ruth, 1941-; Saff, Donald, 1937-; Rosenthal, Nan
    - "Inside New York's Art World." Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel and the New School for Social Research., 1977; Castelli, Leo; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate of analog video recording; 00:27:32
    - Museum of Contemporary Art, Los Angeles, circa 1980; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings (Box 37, Object 1, Reg number 210.V004.00)
  - Lectures and symposia
    - "Art Meets Science and Spirituality in a Changing Economy"
      - "Art Meets Science and Spirituality in a Changing Economy." Maxine Harris and Louwrien Wijers., 1993; 0.10 Cubic Feet; 5 Video Recordings distribution copies (Box 8, Object 10, Object 11, Object 12, Object 13, Object 14)
        Parts 1-5 of "Art Meets Science and Spirituality in a Changing Economy" series.
      - Event footage, 1990; Bohm, David, 1917-1992; Bstan-ʼdzin-rgya-mtsho, Dalai Lama XIV, 1935-; 0.07 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings PAL submaster; NTSC duplicate (Box 37, Object 4, Reg number 90.V003.00, Box 8, Object 9, Reg number 93.V003.00)
        Bohm, David, 1917-1992; Bstan-ʼdzin-rgya-mtsho, Dalai Lama XIV, 1935-
    - "Dialogues in Contemporary Art: Robert Rauschenberg and Dave Hickey," MoCA, Los Angeles, 2001 March 18; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog access copy and digital surrogate; 01:38:29 (Box 8, Object 15, Reg number 201.V003.00)
    - Dyslexia seminar, SMU Meadows School of the Arts, 1989 November 7; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings raw footage; 2 analog video recordings and 1 digital surrogate; 01:00:01 (Box 8, Object 16, Reg number 98.V016.00, Object 17)
    - "James Rosenquist and Robert Rauschenberg at the Guggenheim", 2003 December 16; Rosenquist, James, 1933-; Hopps, Walter; Bancroft, Sarah C.; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 3 Video Recordings 2 analog video recordings and 1 digital surrogate; 01:07:26 (Box 8, Object 18, Reg number 203.V005.00, Object 19, Reg number 203.V006.00)
      Rosenquist, James, 1933-; Hopps, Walter; Bancroft, Sarah C.
    - Wexner Prize lectures
      - "A Completely Biased Homage to Robert Rauschenberg." Robert Hughes., 2000 May 31; Hughes, Robert, 1938-2012; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate; o1:04:00 (Box 8, Object 21, Reg number 200.V008.00)
        Hughes, Robert, 1938-2012
      - "Robert Rauschenberg Symposium", 2000 May 19; Rainer, Yvonne, 1934-; Gehry, Frank O., 1929-; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate; 01:20:00 (Box 8, Object 22, Reg number 200.V010.00)
        Rainer, Yvonne, 1934-; Gehry, Frank O., 1929-
  - Legal
    Restriction
    This file is restricted for reasons regarding confidentiality.
    - Battle Fowler, 1994 February - March; 0.025 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings interfiled footage log and correspondence camera original and duplicate (Box 8, Object 26, Box 32, Object 8, Reg number 94.V004.00)
  - Memorial
    - Barbara B. Mann Auditorium, Edison Community College, 2008; 80 Video Recordings 80 digital video recordings
    - "Elegy for Robert Rauschenberg." Art21., 2008; Brown, Earle, 1926-2002; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate; 00:09:35
    - Metropolitan Museum of Art, 2008; 0.08 Cubic Feet; 9 Video Recordings 8 camera originals and 1 digital surrogate; 01:59:12 (Box 33, Object 9, Object 10, Object 11, Object 12, Object 13, Object 14, Object 15, Object 16)
    - Museum of Contemporary of Art, Los Angeles, circa 2008; 1 Video Recordings digital surrogate; 02:05:44
      Database record reads "Robert Rauschenberg Celebration of Life."
    - "Robert Rauschenberg, 1925-2008", circa 2008; 0.04 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings (Box 8, Object 23, Reg number 209.V005.00, Object 24, Reg number 209.V006.00)
  - Radio
    - Newscasts, circa 1975; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Sound Recordings polyester audio tape; 1.875 ips; mono 1/4 inch (Box 35, Object 38, Reg number 75.A005.00, Object 39, Reg number 75.A005.01)
  - Social and political
    - Segment on artists' political funding. CBS News., 1980; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings duplicate of broadcast video recording and digital surrogate; 00:04:34 (Box 8, Object 25, Reg number 80.V003.00)
    - U.S. House debate on UDC acquisition of "The Dinner Party", 1990 July 26; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate (Box 8, Object 26)
      Chicago, Judy, 1939-
    - U.S. Senate hearing on Bork appointment, 1987 September 22; 0.25 Cubic Feet; 4 Video Recordings 3 analog duplicates and 1 digital surrogate; 00:57:16 (Box 37, Object 20, Reg number 87.V004.00, Box 8, Object 1, Object 28)
  - Television and serials
    - "ART today," Volume III, Number 1, 1991 February; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings video magazine (Box 8, Object 2, Reg number 91.V040.00)
    - "Imagining America: Icons of the 20th Century." Muse Film and Television., circa 2005; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings off-air broadcast recording (Box 8, Object 3, Reg number 205.V001.01)
    - Interview with Anne Boa. CKVU-TV Vancouver., circa 1973-1980; 0.05 Cubic Feet; 1 Video Recordings duplicate of broadcast video recording (Box 37, Object 9, Reg number 210.V003.00)
    - Japan Art Association interview. Fuji TV, Japan., 1998 June 1; 0.02 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog rough cut and digital surrogate; 0:30:00; 00:32:26 (Box 8, Object 4, Reg number 98.V015.00)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg" raw footage. Good Morning America., 1980 January 11; 0.05 Cubic Feet; 2 Video Recordings analog raw footage duplicate and digital surrogate; 00:52:11 (Box 37, Object 19, Reg number 80.V001.00)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg." U.S.A. Artists. WNET, circa 1966; 1 Cubic Feet; 5 Video Recordings film transfer master; 4 digital betacam transfers; 4 Motion Picture Films interfiled footage log outtakes and composite; B&W; positive; 1 optical sound track and 3 silent 16 mm (Box 37, Object 15, Reg number 85.V030.00, Box 47, Object 2, Reg number 211.MM002.01, Object 5, Reg number 211.MM002.02, Object 6, Reg number 211.MM002.00, Box 8, Object 4, Object 7, Reg number 211.A001.00, Box 52)
    - "Robert Rauschenberg: Inventive Genius." American Masters., Thomas, Karen
      - Edited masters and clip reels, 1998-1999; 0.142 Cubic Feet; 6 Video Recordings 4 analog edited master, excerpts and duplicates, 2 digital surrogates of full program; NTSC; PAL; 00:56:26 (Box 8, Object 5, Reg number 98.V009.00, Object 6, Reg number 99.V002.01, Object 20, Reg number 99.V002.5, Object 21, Reg number 98.V010.00, Box 30, Object 17, Reg number 99.V002.4)